this exercise has
asked us to determine the difference
between the two hashes that we see in
this code
my hash is initialized on line two
and you can see that there's a colon
after the x
the key in this hash is a symbol on line
we also see an x but in this case
x is not a symbol x is the local
variable that we initialized on line 1.
this variable references the string hi
there
now to see the difference let's print
both of these hashes
when we print these two hashes with p we
can see the symbol that is the key of
the first hash
and in the second hash we see the string
high there
as the key and again this is because
when we initialized the second hash
on line three we use the local variable
x as the key which references the string
hi there